cross the wide end over the narrow end
making an x grab hold the center of the
x step one is behind take the wide end
of the tie and make it go behind the tie
hole the back of the tie should now be
showing step two is in
take the wide end of the tie and make it
go in the tie hole
the back of the tie should again be
showing step three is across
take the wide end of the tie and make it
go across the tie hole tip keep a finger
here
the front of the tie should now be
showing
step 4 is out
take the wide end of the tie and make it
go out of the tie hole to finish it up
put the wide end of the tie where your
finger is and pull it through tip
squeeze the bottom of the knot and pull
the tops apart to create the triangular
shape another tip as you pull the knot
tight you can use a finger to try to
create the dimple tighten the knot
around your neck by holding the narrow
end and sliding the knot up